[
{"id":"1","sort":"1","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前10000名","front":"9001","back":"10000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"2","sort":"2","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前9000名","front":"8001","back":"9000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"3","sort":"3","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前8000名","front":"7001","back":"8000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"4","sort":"4","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前7000名","front":"6001","back":"7000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"5","sort":"5","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前6000名","front":"5001","back":"6000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"6","sort":"6","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前5000名","front":"4001","back":"5000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"7","sort":"7","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前4000名","front":"3001","back":"4000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"8","sort":"8","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前3000名","front":"2001","back":"3000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"9","sort":"9","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前2000名","front":"1001","back":"2000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"10","sort":"10","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前1000名","front":"901","back":"1000","reward":"100"},
{"id":"11","sort":"11","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前900名","front":"801","back":"900","reward":"100"},
{"id":"12","sort":"12","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前800名","front":"701","back":"800","reward":"100"},
{"id":"13","sort":"13","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前700名","front":"601","back":"700","reward":"100"},
{"id":"14","sort":"14","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前600名","front":"501","back":"600","reward":"100"},
{"id":"15","sort":"15","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前500名","front":"401","back":"500","reward":"100"},
{"id":"16","sort":"16","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前400名","front":"301","back":"400","reward":"100"},
{"id":"17","sort":"17","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前300名","front":"201","back":"300","reward":"100"},
{"id":"18","sort":"18","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前200名","front":"101","back":"200","reward":"100"},
{"id":"19","sort":"19","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前100名","front":"11","back":"100","reward":"100"},
{"id":"20","sort":"20","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前10名","front":"7","back":"10","reward":"100"},
{"id":"21","sort":"21","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前6名","front":"4","back":"6","reward":"100"},
{"id":"22","sort":"22","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前3名","front":"3","back":"3","reward":"100"},
{"id":"23","sort":"23","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前2名","front":"2","back":"2","reward":"100"},
{"id":"24","sort":"24","tips1":"1小时金币","tips2":"首次进入排行榜前1名","front":"1","back":"1","reward":"100"}
]